[Home](https://fileinfo.com/) Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

Updated August 24, 2023

This Privacy Policy explains how Sharpened Productions, Inc (a.k.a. "Sharpened") collects, uses, and safeguards information and data that it collects from your use of FileInfo.com.

As a basic rule, Sharpened does not collect personally identifiable information. However, that doesn’t mean that we don’t collect any information about your use of our website. It is recommended that you read this entire policy before interacting with our website or accessing our service as it informs you of our data collection, retention, and use policies, and will help you better understand your rights concerning these policies.

As with the [Terms of Use](https://fileinfo.com/terms), and as a condition of using this website and service, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not, or cannot, consent to the terms of this Policy, then you should immediately cease accessing the service and leave the website. Continued use of the website and access of the service demonstrates your acceptance of the entirety of our Privacy Policy.

### 1\. Personal Information

FileInfo.com is free to use and does not require you to enter personal information or create an account to use the website or access our service. We do not require that you supply us with identifying information such as your name, address, date of birth, race or ethnicity, or financial information in order to utilize our website. We will never collect information on you, such as genetic data, health information, religious affiliation, or other sensitive or protected information for any reason.

The only time we will collect identifying information or contact details from you are when you voluntarily submit a message through our [contact form](https://fileinfo.com/contact). Information shared in this manner will be stored on servers under which only we and our authorized third parties have access. This information will be used only to respond to your message. You may request that we delete your personally identifiable information at any time, and your request will be honored promptly.

Similar to most websites on the Internet, the FileInfo.com server logs visitor IP address and browser information. This information is used solely for analytical purposes, to improve our services, and to identify threats. We will not share this information with unauthorized third parties or use it to personally identify you.

### 2\. Third-Party Data

FileInfo.com may share non-personal, non-identifying data with third-party advertising and analytics services for the following purposes:

1. To fulfill service requests and to perform business functions (e.g data hosting services; packaging, mailing and delivering services; and customer support).
2. As required by law or to protect Sharpened in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process served on Sharpened; (b) protect and defend Sharpened’s rights or property; or (c) protect the personal safety of Sharpened’s personnel or members of the public in appropriate circumstances.
3. If Sharpened and/or its assets (or a portion of its assets) are sold, assigned, transferred, or merged, or if Sharpened undergoes some other change including a change to its corporate form as part of a bankruptcy proceeding or otherwise; information may be transferred as part of that transaction or change.
4. To offer you products and services that may be of interest to you.
5. Providing usage analytics and insights for improving the website or service’s overall function.
6. Identifying threats and addressing disruptions of the website and service to ensure its smooth and safe functionality.

### 3\. Website Analytics

FileInfo.com uses Google Analytics to monitor and analyze website traffic. For details about how data are collected and used, including how to opt out, refer to [Google Analytics Help](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245) and the [Google Privacy Policy](https://policies.google.com/privacy).

### 4\. Website Advertising

We partner with Google and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to our website and other websites to provide advertisements of interest to you. To learn more about online advertising and your options for opting out, visit the [NAI opt-out page](https://thenai.org/opt-out/).

You should be aware that other internet websites that are linked from this website or from an email message we send you may contain privacy provisions that differ from the provisions of this Privacy Policy. To ensure your privacy is protected, we recommend that you review the privacy statements of these other linked sites, applications, or other digital platforms.

### 5\. Cookies

To enhance and individualize your experience on FileInfo.com, we may use small files called "cookies" that allow us to know that you are a prior user and help us ensure that appropriate information is directed to you. For example, cookies are set to remember your theme and font preferences. Cookie settings can be controlled in your web browser to automatically reject some forms of cookies. If you view our website without changing your cookie settings, you are indicating your consent to receive all cookies from the site. If you do not allow cookies, some features and functionality of the website may not operate as expected.

In addition, we permit third-party ad networks to also set and access cookies, the function of which are subject to terms and the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. These ad networks use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site, but we cannot warrant or guarantee how this information will be used or who else it may be shared with when it leaves our website.

### 6\. Data Retention

We implement commercially-reasonable security measures and features to protect user information and prevent unauthorized use, access, modification, destruction, disclosure, transfer, or other misappropriations of information from our website. We will store the information that we received from our contact form in a secure location in which only we and authorized parties have access. We will also delete identifying information that we received through our contact form as soon as it is no longer required to achieve the purpose for which it was collected.

The servers that host our website and services are provided by third parties that maintains them in a secure environment. However, we cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of every piece of data or information provided to it, or of every communication transmitted to us.

### 7\. Data Access

Information collected from your use of FileInfo.com is processed in the United States, where privacy laws may be less stringent than the laws in other countries, and where the government, courts, or law enforcement may be able to access your data. By utilizing our website, you agree to the transfer, storage and processing of your data and information in the United States.

You, as the data subject, have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority, in particular in the Member State of your habitual residence, place of work, or place of the alleged infringement, if you believe that the processing of your personal data does not comply with legal requirements.

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please [contact us](https://fileinfo.com/contact).
